hi my name is Mitra Kornilov and it's a
嗨，我叫米特拉·科尼洛夫（Mitra Kornilov）
JSON support in a Java Enterprise
Java Enterprise中的JSON支持
Edition age coding session we will start
我们将开始版本年龄编码会议
with a little bit of legal stuff so this
有一点合法的东西，所以这
is safe harbor statement which basically
是基本的安全港声明
says that what I'm going to talk today
说我今天要说的
what I'm going to demonstrate could be
我要演示的可能是
not a part of for the final product so
不是最终产品的一部分，所以
you shouldn't make critical business
你不应该做关键业务
decisions based on that now a little bit
基于此的决策现在有点
about myself I don't have a capture in
关于我自己我没有被抓住
software which supports
支持的软件
picture-in-picture so I can't make it
画中画，所以我做不到
the day as other doing there the corner
和其他人一样在角落里度过的一天
of the screen you see my picture my
在屏幕上看到我的照片
video talking so I just put my photo
视频聊天，所以我只放我的照片
here it's how I look like I'm from
这就是我来自哪里的样子
Oracle I am Jason Biden congestion
Oracle我是Jason Biden拥塞
processing spec leads last year was
去年处理规格线索的原因是
awarded as outstanding spec lead which
被授予杰出的技术领先者
are very proud of I'm also open source
我为自己也开源感到自豪
enthusiast and eclipse link project
爱好者和日食链接项目
comida
科米达
enough introduction let's actually start
足够的介绍让我们开始
coding and this session is organized
编码，本次会议是有组织的
today that I created a project template
今天我创建了一个项目模板
which is a using JSON processing and
这是使用JSON处理的
Jason binding and I will demonstrate
Jason binding，我将演示
live how to use adjacent proteases and
现场如何使用相邻的蛋白酶和
Jason binding features from very very
Jason的绑定功能非常非常
easy from very simple ones to some
从非常简单的东西到一些简单的东西
advanced ones and I will also
高级的，我也会
demonstrate how to use JSON processing
演示如何使用JSON处理
condition binding together the result of
条件绑定在一起的结果
that I will put into this repository
我将放入该存储库
alright maybe I will clean it up a bit
好吧，也许我会收拾一下
maybe I'll put some comments there to
也许我会在这里发表一些评论
make it nicer before putting it there so
在把它放好之前先弄好
don't expect that it's exactly the same
不要指望完全一样
as you see
正如你看到的
you will see today but it will be a same
你今天会看到，但是会一样
from the functionality point of view so
从功能的角度来看
this is how my project looks like you
这就是我的项目看起来像你的样子
see that this is a maven project it has
看到这是一个Maven项目
only three classes here and through the
这里只有三节课
model classes I will touch them when I
模特班，我会碰他们
will talk about JSON binding this is the
将谈论JSON绑定，这是
console application I already pre filled
我已经预填充的控制台应用程序
some of the UI themes here so we won't
这里的一些UI主题，所以我们不会
lose time coordinate so when you run it
失去时间坐标，所以在运行时
it will show these texts and you select
它会显示这些文本，然后您选择
the number you should type the number
您应该输入数字的数字
which do you want to run and the GMOs
您想经营哪些以及GMO
are listed here so I have 8 things to
在这里列出，所以我有八件事
demonstrate we'll start adjacent
演示我们将开始相邻
processor and after that we will go to
处理器，然后我们将转到
Jason binding right well actually you
杰森实际上很好地绑定了你
select the demo it runs the
选择运行的演示
corresponding methods itís even methods
对应的方法甚至是方法
here and currently this methods are
这里和目前这种方法是
empty so I also not Oleg and I empty
空的，所以我也不是奥列格，我空的
this is not empty but as you see this is
这不是空的，但是如您所见，这是空的
just data preparation nothing else right
只是数据准备就没事了
and I will cause I will add codes to
我会导致我将代码添加到
these methods you know online unity
您知道在线团结这些方法
session over else resources which is
在其他资源上的会话
what the JSON documents I'm going to use
我将使用什么JSON文档
for my samples and important I suppose
对于我的样品，我想很重要
is this this is for maximal main file
这是最大的主文件吗
which is also very simple let us go
这也很简单，让我们走吧
through these quickly dependencies I
通过这些快速的依赖我
have only four dependencies and these
只有四个依赖项，这些
are Jason protesting API is I'm using
我正在使用Jason抗议API
milestone 1 version Jason producing RI
里程碑1版本Jason生产RI
as base and the same for Jason binding
作为基础，与Jason绑定相同
API and RI which is yassun and in order
yassun的API和RI
to add yeah so here I've had
添加是的，所以我在这里
and this repository here because yes
这个仓库在这里，因为是的
only uses eclipse foundation
只使用蚀基础
repositories it has its so release
它有这样的版本库
repository mission space right built
正确建立了仓库任务空间
section is also very simple where are
部分也很简单
only free plugins compiler with 1.8
只有1.8的免费插件编译器
target and source simply plug in and
目标和源只需插入并
exact plug-in because I want to run my
确切的插件，因为我想运行我的
application from console main let's just
从控制台主应用程序开始
take a look how it looks like if I
看一下我的样子
compile Clinton's soul and exact Java so
编译克林顿的灵魂和确切的Java
based on building the project and
基于构建项目并
running it oh see maybe what builds all
运行它，哦，也许是所有的东西
first time it usually takes time
第一次通常需要时间
no it was relatively quick so you see
不，它相对较快，所以您看到了
this UI right and you select the DMO you
正确的用户界面，然后选择DMO
want to start and nothing happens
想开始，什么也没发生
because these methods are empty at the
因为这些方法在
moment so I need to queue to creat ok
片刻，所以我需要排队来确定
now let's open our demo and start coding
现在让我们打开演示并开始编码
something Jason parson demo demonstrate
Jason Parson演示演示的东西
parsing of JSON document so what's all
解析JSON文档，这就是全部
about I will show how to open JSON
关于我将展示如何打开JSON
document how to use JSON parser and the
文档如何使用JSON解析器和
task is to list all the parts in events
任务是列出事件中的所有部分
and the corresponding keys in values and
以及相应的值键和
after that ultimately how to skip some
之后，最终如何跳过一些
part of your document if it's be Jason
是Jason文件的一部分
Jason so this is the document I'm going
杰森，这是我要去的文件
to use for the app so as you see this is
用于该应用程序，如您所见，这是
a JSON document in the least and at
至少在JSON文档
least of free Jason's Jason Bourne super
至少免费的Jason's Jason Bourne super
agent it has some phone numbers so you
代理商，它有一些电话号码，所以你
can phone him if you want another one is
可以给他打电话的话
Jason Voorhees remember of right is 13
Jason Voorhees记得正确的是13
so he is a maniac killer he also had
所以他也是一个疯子杀手
some phone numbers
一些电话号码
I'm not recommending giving him a cover
我不建议给他掩护
and the last one is Jason from the Asian
最后一个是亚洲人的杰森
Greece he's the lead of Argonauts if you
希腊，如果您愿意，他是Argonauts的领导者
remember what's bad right he doesn't
记住他没有什么不好
have any phone numbers because that time
有任何电话号码，因为那个时候
phones didn't exist right anyway okay so
手机根本不存在，所以
let's just open this document and the
让我们打开此文档，然后
parser parse it parser works the way
解析器解析它解析器的工作方式
that it just goes through the document
它只是通过文档
and the Banat gets when it reaches meet
巴纳特人到达时会见面
some jason related field or talking or
一些与杰森有关的领域或谈话或
whatever it's basically then right so
基本上不管是什么，所以
let's just create a parcel jsonparser
让我们创建一个包裹jsonparser
parser it's imported equals to jason dot
解析器的导入等于jason dot
create parcel so jason t has these jason
创建包裹，让杰森t有这些杰森
class right I just don't see what it has
上课的权利，我只是不知道它有什么
it has methods to create a refeed
它具有创建重新加载的方法
factory methods right here's some
工厂方法就在这里
builders batch generator blah blah blah
建设者批处理发电机等等等等等等
a lot of things right so when you need
很多事情都对，所以当您需要时
to create you always know that you need
创建你总是知道你需要
to create it from J subclass so it's
从J子类创建它，因此
very simple create parser and we need to
非常简单的创建解析器，我们需要
pass the input stream to this parser
将输入流传递到此解析器
like these a get resources stream and we
像这样获得资源流，我们
are going to read our Jason's Jason
要读我们杰森的杰森
document okay so we have a parser now we
文档好，所以我们现在有一个解析器
need to parse a document how to do it we
需要解析一个文档我们该怎么做
need to have a cycle which cycles until
需要有一个循环，直到
parser has next event looks very similar
解析器的下一个事件看起来非常相似
to if you are working files in a similar
如果您正在使用类似的文件
way so now we need to get the event
这样，现在我们需要获取事件
itself and we use parse the next method
本身，我们使用解析下一个方法
which was the event so event E right
这是事件，所以事件E对
I'll say this and now we'll just print
我会这样说，现在我们只打印
out name of event and let's run it and
列出事件的名称，然后运行它，
see how it works
看看它怎么运作
compile it slow yeah got it running
编译它很慢，是的，它运行了
number one the mo and you see already
莫一号，你已经看到了
real so here if we open our JSON
真实，所以如果我们打开JSON
document you see that when parser
您在解析器时看到的文档
reached just talking it start array
到达只是在说它开始数组
start the Raven traced enough then go
启动足够跟踪的乌鸦然后走
start object which is here and after
开始对象在这里和之后
that goes key which is name and after
那是名称和之后的关键
that radio still adjacent ball blah blah
那个收音机仍然靠近球等等
blah blah blah blah and when it reaches
等等等等等等，当它到达时
the end of the array or the end of
数组的末尾或
object it has end object and the Ravens
对象，它具有最终对象和乌鸦
right so this way it parses all the
对，这样它解析所有
document so what are we going to do now
文档，所以我们现在要做什么
we are going to email it reaches the key
我们将通过电子邮件发送它到达关键
we will just print out the name of the
我们将只打印出名称
key when it reaches the value it just
当它达到值时就关键
prints out we will print out the value
打印出来，我们将打印出值
let's do that close it run to the demo
让我们关闭它运行演示
okay so in this case we need to
好的，在这种情况下，我们需要
distinguish their bets right so when we
正确区分他们的赌注，这样当我们
get this key name or wave enters value
获取此键名或wave输入值
string will print this value if some
字符串将打印此值，如果一些
other way we have to just keep that
否则我们必须保持
right so in order to do it we just need
对，所以为了做到这一点，我们只需要
a switch statement here switch sorry
开关声明在这里切换对不起
switch event right and in case it's key
切换事件的权利，以防万一
name or in case it's very string we will
名称，或者如果它是非常字符串，我们将
just print out the value parser gets
只需打印出值解析器获取
trick
特技
so which parcel get still croissants
那么哪个包裹仍然有羊角面包
actually the value from education
实际上是教育的价值
document to make it a bit nicer or we
文档使其变得更好，或者我们
need to remove print line here making
需要在这里删除打印线
just three
只是三个
and make it like this and okay let's do
让它像这样，好吧，让我们做
it this way we need to find break that
这样我们需要找到突破
doesn't look good I think so let's just
看起来不太好，我想所以
check it okay I forgot to creat Street
确认一下，我忘了创建Street
and compile it again my computer's
并再次编译我的计算机
rolling now when I'm starting compile it
现在开始编译时滚动
just was like that hopefully you won't
只是希望你不会
hear this but I hear that okay it's done
听到了，但我听到，好了
and you see that if it's key key name
然后您会看到它是否为键名
when you steal Jason Bourne blah blah
当您偷Jason Bourne等等时
blah it looks great
等等看起来很棒
okay so I assume that the first two
好吧，所以我认为前两个
tasks are completed but we still have a
任务已经完成，但是我们还有一个
third one imagine that imagine that
第三个人想像
these phone numbers array is huge Jason
这些电话号码数组是巨大的杰森
Voorhees a super agent he works in
Voorhees是他工作的超级经纪人
different countries I suppose if in each
我想如果每个国家都不同
country he has a phone number maybe many
他有一个国家的电话号码，也许很多
phone numbers he changes from numbers
他从号码更改的电话号码
every day you know super agent so his
每天你都知道超级特工，所以他
phone numbers array can be huge and we
电话号码数组可能很大，我们
don't want to parse it we want to skip
不想解析我们想跳过
it right so how to do it it's very easy
没错，所以怎么做很容易
and because Jason P version 1.1 has
并且因为Jason P版本1.1具有
methods which allows you to skip erase
跳过擦除的方法
and skip objects basically when you
基本上当你跳过对象
inside immediately go to the end of it
里面马上走到它的尽头
right so it means that in case we are
对，所以这意味着如果我们
either a we need to skip it parser skip
要么我们需要跳过它解析器跳过
array right but now if I keep it like
数组正确，但是现在，如果我保持它像
that
那
it won't work because the document
它不会起作用，因为该文档
itself is the least is the array right
本身至少是数组的权利
so start rings are first element
所以启动环是第一要素
so it will just don't do anything we
所以它什么也不会做
need to only skip phone numbers array in
只需要跳过其中的电话号码数组
order to do that I will introduce a
为了做到这一点，我将介绍一个
string
串
where we'll hold the current key we're
我们将保持当前密钥的位置
in so slightly modify our sample that in
稍微修改一下我们的样本
case you meet the key we just put it
如果您遇到钥匙，我们就把它放好
into our variable yes you need to print
到我们的变量中，是的，您需要打印
it right you need to print it and hang
正确，您需要打印并挂起
it right here right and if if these key
就在这里，如果这些关键
equals four numbers I need to skip array
等于我需要跳过数组的四个数字
and break right so that's good news
然后中断，这是个好消息
yeah it's okay so let's just run it and
是的没关系，所以让我们运行它，
check up a little bit again check that
再检查一下
it works I have a feeling that
它有效，我有一种感觉
compilation slower and slower because
编译越来越慢，因为
we're aging the code there may be its
我们正在老化代码，可能是
objective okay number one okay I choose
客观，好的，我选择第一，好的
like working so you see that we have
喜欢工作，所以你看到我们有
starter and after that wedge up it'll
初学者，然后楔入它会
end object immediately right so we don't
立即终止对象，这样我们就不会
have phone numbers here oh we have a key
这里有电话号码，哦，我们有钥匙
for numbers but what inside is skipped
数字，但里面的内容被跳过
so this is actually exactly what we
所以这实际上正是我们
wanted so huge phone numbers array we
想要如此庞大的电话号码数组，我们
just skip okay so we finish through the
只是跳过好吧，所以我们完成了
first demo let's jump to another one and
第一个演示让我们跳到另一个
Jason generated them oh and here we will
杰森（Jason）生成了它们，哦，在这里我们将
generate a document similar to jason
生成类似于jason的文档
jason in the course sometimes you need
杰森在课程中有时您需要
to generate jason in the code to do it
在代码中生成杰森来做到这一点
Jason B has a class called jason
杰森B的班级叫杰森
generator now just create it
生成器现在只需创建它
I call it Jan right then again if you
我再称它为Jan
need to create something I need to go to
需要创建一些我需要去的东西
Jason class right create generator beta
杰森（Jason）类权创建生成器Beta
to cast and here we need to pass where
进行投射，我们需要在此处传递
actually we want to generate it right
实际上我们想正确生成它
out output stream and we will use system
输出流，我们将使用系统
out for the scripts
出脚本
okay so we created the generator now
好的，所以我们现在创建了发电机
let's start generate and the first
让我们开始生成，第一个
element is basically we have a list of
元素基本上是我们的列表
Jason's right so first element is a
杰森（Jason）的权利，所以第一个要素是
start
开始
all right right star all right and after
好吧好吧明星吧好吧之后
that we are going to put the third JSON
我们将要放置第三个JSON
object I mean Jason Bourne here object
我的意思是Jason Bourne这里的对象
containing Jason board here so we need
在这里包含杰森板，所以我们需要
to write start objects right you see
马上写起始对象
that a generator has a nice builder
发电机有一个不错的建造者
interface which is very easy to use so
界面非常易于使用，因此
after that we need to write our stores
之后，我们需要写我们的商店
property right and the key is name and
产权，关键是名称和
the value is Jason Bourne
值是Jason Bourne
and then Jason board like that and the
然后像这样的Jason Board和
second property is profession if I
如果我是第二产业的话
remember well profession and the his
记得很好的职业和他的
profession is super-agent right and
专业是超级代理人的权利，
after that goes array with phone numbers
之后再加上电话号码
so we need to write start array and now
所以我们需要写开始数组
we need actually pass a key here right
我们实际上需要在这里传递密钥
four numbers right
四个数字正确
and inside there again we need to write
再在里面，我们需要写
start object and in that object we have
起始对象，在那个对象中
two properties first of all is tied for
首先有两个属性
type of phone number so it's home and
电话号码的类型，所以它是家
actually the number itself so right
实际上，数字本身很正确
number and if I remember well number is
数字，如果我记得很好，数字是
like that it's not because I am phoning
这样不是因为我在打电话
him a lot just because number is very
他很多，只是因为人数非常多
simple and this is the end of the object
很简单，这就是对象的终点
so we need to write the end of the
所以我们需要写完
object right and JSONP has one method
对象权限，JSONP有一种方法
right and to write and to end everything
正确的写作和结束一切
so
所以
it's used for the end of an object and
它用于对象的结尾，
for the end of array so we are closing
对于数组的末尾，所以我们要关闭
the object now we are closing this array
现在关闭该数组的对象
now we are closing out a small object
现在我们要关闭一个小物体
and here we are
我们在这里
Oh closing our three and what also have
哦，关闭我们的三个，还有什么
to look at the flashes and it looks like
看一下闪光灯，看起来像
that's it then just start it and see how
就是这样，然后启动它，看看如何
it works like forgetting to create all
它就像忘记创建所有
the time so let's compile it it's
时间，让我们来编译它
supposed to produce like a source part
应该像源零件一样生产
of our JSON JSON document I use in the
我在JSON JSON文档中使用的
first sample let's take a look here and
第一个样本让我们在这里看看
here this array first object Jason
这里这个数组的第一个对象杰森
Bourne super agent phone numbers blah
伯恩超级经纪人电话号码等等
blah blah blah blah blah so it works
等等等等等等等等
great so now we can go to the fourth
太好了，现在我们可以转到第四
sample and for example is streaming API
示例，例如流API
right so in JSONP 1.1 we added support
正确，因此在JSONP 1.1中，我们添加了支持
for Java 8 streaming API so we can
Java 8流API，因此我们可以
actually read the JSON object and using
实际读取JSON对象并使用
steaming API to do something like that
蒸API做类似的事情
and from this sample I will use another
从这个样本中，我将使用另一个
JSON document I prepared and this is a
我准备的JSON文档，这是一个
list of like a shopping cart and here I
像购物车的清单，我在这里
have again this is the least and it has
再次有这是最少的，它有
free object there so it's what I bind
那里有自由物体，这就是我绑定的东西
and by Martin ball 400 bucks and buying
并通过马丁球400美元购买
a video card for 500 bucks
一张500美元的视频卡
so it is nice fun it's supposed to
所以它应该很好玩
collect an 18 g-force or something like
收集18克力或类似的东西
that and I buy the PC case which is a
那我买了一个PC机箱
quick cheap for hungrybox I'm not sure
不确定饿的盒子便宜吗
that I'll be able to assemble a nice PC
我将能够组装好的PC
from that but anyway this is just a
从那开始，但是无论如何这只是一个
demonstration right and our what are we
示范权，我们是什么
going to do we are going to use
将要使用的东西
streaming API to get the total of the
流API以获取
cars right
正确的汽车
count dude first of all we need to read
伯爵首先需要阅读
the JSON document and we will use JSON
JSON文档，我们将使用JSON
the reader for that Jason the reader
那个杰森的读者
reader sorry
读者抱歉
later equals to again Jason create
以后等于再次杰森创造
reader and we are going to create reader
阅读器，我们将创建阅读器
from our card document card yes right
来自我们的证件卡是
now we need to read everything to JSON
现在我们需要将所有内容读取为JSON
array because its array jason array now
数组，因为它的数组jason数组现在
actually do it the other way around so
实际上是反过来做的
because I need to demonstrate a
因为我需要证明一个
streaming API so the less you see is
流式API，因此您所看到的更少
reader we need to read array right like
读者，我们需要像这样读取数组
that and that read array it has a method
那和那个读取数组它有一个方法
called stream so get a rest sleep so now
叫溪，所以要休息一下
we can use our streaming API right so we
我们可以正确使用流式API，所以我们
need to oh no need to collect all right
需要哦，不需要收集所有权利
writes just need to collect because we
写只是需要收集，因为我们
actually need a map right we need to map
实际上需要一张地图，我们需要绘制地图
and not map we need to map to double
而不是映射，我们需要映射为两倍
because double the price is double right
因为双倍的价格是双倍的权利
now we put a simple lambda here which
现在我们在这里放一个简单的lambda
actually extracts the price from our
实际上是从我们那里提取价格
objects there and lambda will look
在那里的对象和lambda将看起来
something like this we need to get the
这样的事情，我们需要得到
object as JSON object right so mist we
对象作为JSON对象，所以我们迷雾了
got our JSON object which has a name and
得到了我们的JSON对象，其名称和
price here right and we need to get a
价格在这里，我们需要得到一个
number value for a property a City
一个城市的属性的数字值
properties price if I remember well it
物业价格，如果我还记得的话
is check quickly yeah name and price
是很快检查耶和名称和价格
okay and back price and we need to get a
好吧，回价格，我们需要得到一个
double value of that so it's easy as
两倍的价值，所以很容易
that and after that we just need to
在那之后，我们只需要
summarize all this that's it
总结所有这些
and to print it out I just do I just put
并打印出来，我只是把
it to variable and I print out this
它到变量，我打印出来
variable here let's just run it and see
变量在这里，让我们运行它看看
does it work or not and the amount of a
它有效与否以及
total amount will be supposed to be 700
总金额应该是700
bucks if I remember well this yeah
如果我记得很好的话，是的
700 so look it works so and this is how
700看起来如此工作，这就是方法
to use Java it seems a streaming API
使用Java似乎是流式API
with JSON processing okay now we are
JSON处理好了，现在
jumped into the interesting bit which is
跳到有趣的地方是
JSON pointer this is a feature of JSONP
JSON指针，这是JSONP的功能
1.1 and which is one of the most
1.1，这是最重要的之一
requested features and here I will
请求的功能，在这里我会
demonstrate how to create Jason pointer
演示如何创建Jason指针
and how to print out its value hi
以及如何打印出它的值
first of all left-click pointer let's
首先，左键点击
use our Jason's document and create a
使用我们的Jason文档并创建一个
pointer to profession of the first Jason
指向第一个杰森职业的指针
Bourne right it will look like first of
伯恩吧，它看起来像是
all we need to create a Jason pointer
我们需要创建一个Jason指针
again P Jason create pointer right and
再次，P Jason创建了正确的指针，
then sign the pointer we need to put a
然后在指针上签名，我们需要放一个
string which is something like XPath
类似于XPath的字符串
inside the JSON document so we always
在JSON文档中，所以我们总是
start with the root and because it's
从根开始，因为它是
array we need to get the first element
我们需要获取第一个元素的数组
of the array which is 0 and after that
数组的0，之后
we are getting a profession property
我们正在获得职业财产
here it is it's very simple
这很简单
now we need to apply this pointer to
现在我们需要将此指针应用于
some JSON documents to extract this
一些JSON文档来提取这个
value from there so basically we need to
那里的价值，所以基本上我们需要
read our Jason's as you can copy it from
阅读我们的Jason，因为您可以从
here yeah
是啊
so we're reading our Jason's documents
所以我们正在阅读Jason的文档
and let's just create an array jason
然后让我们创建一个数组jason
array Jason's and it's imported from the
数组Jason's，它是从
reader reader iterate so we have Jason's
读者读者迭代，所以我们有杰森的
right now and now we can apply this
现在，我们现在可以应用此
pointer to the document right so it does
指向文档的指针正确
it it works away that pointer and it has
它可以解决那个指针，并且具有
getvalue method right and we pass our
getvalue方法正确，我们通过了
Jason's here right and it's supposed to
杰森就在这里，应该
get the value corresponding to this
得到与此对应的值
pointer from them so it's Jason value
他们的指针，所以这就是杰森的价值
Jason value profession and print it out
杰森重视职业并打印出来
precision to string let's see what we
字符串的精度让我们看看我们
will have
将有
combining compiling yeah and this is
结合编译是的，这是
number four and it doesn't work right
第四个，它不能正常工作
and it says non-existent name when you
并说您不存在的名字
pair in the object blah blah blah key
配对对象等等等等键
profession I made a mistake somewhere
我在某个地方犯了错误
here raw fish
这里生鱼
yeah it looks okay but here is the wrong
是的，看起来还不错，但这是错误的
document because I could be pasted here
文档，因为我可以粘贴在这里
it's supposed to be Jason's right and
应该是杰森的权利，
then I put the card there right sorry
然后我把卡放在那里对不起
about that so let's just try it again
关于这个，让我们再试一次
okay I hope now it works and it does so
好吧，我希望现在可以正常工作了
profession of Jason Bourne super-agents
杰森·伯恩超级经纪人专业
right so just to confirm that it works
对，所以只是为了确认它是否有效
then just change it to this and it
然后将其更改为此
should display a profession of the
应该表现出专业
second Jason right let's just run it and
第二个杰森吧，让我们运行它，
it's supposed to be maniac killer is it
应该是疯子吗
yeah when your killer so this is how
是的，当你的杀手，这是怎么
Jason pointer works okay
杰森指针工作正常
so finish - Jason pointer and the next
完成-Jason指针和下一个
one adjacent page right what is Jason
一页相邻，什么是杰森
page
页
Jason page is basically the ability to
杰森·佩奇（Jason Page）基本上是
pet you Jason document basically change
宠物你杰森文件基本上改变
them or add something thing there or
他们或在那里添加一些东西或
remove things from there it's similar
从那里删除东西就像
you are working with source code
您正在使用源代码
repository to eat for instance right so
例如可以吃的仓库
you have a source file and you create a
您有一个源文件，并创建了一个
patch you change something you create a
修补您更改的内容，然后创建
patch not that you apply the patch to
修补程序不是您将修补程序应用于
that source document to produce new up
该原始文件产生新的
right this is the same vein JSONP right
对，这与JSONP相同
and if diiemma will take out jason's
如果diiemma会拿出jason的
a document and we will create a page
一个文档，我们将创建一个页面
which has multiple things there and it
那里有很多东西
will remove the last Jason from there
将从那里删除最后一个杰森
with only came right and it will replace
只有正确的，它将取代
professions of resource to Jason's right
Jason权利的资源专业
so in order to do it let just read
因此，为了做到这一点，让我们阅读
Jason's document like this I copy pasted
杰森这样的文件我复制粘贴了
here and hopefully it will be right this
在这里，希望这是正确的
time Jason's Jason and we have Jason's
时间杰森的杰森，我们有杰森的
Jason right here now let's create Jason
Jason现在在这里，让我们创建Jason
patch Jason patch right Jason fetch
杰森（Jason）补丁正确杰森（Jason）提取
fetch we use Jason class to create patch
获取我们使用Jason类创建补丁
again but we're going to create page
再次，但是我们要创建页面
builder here we're going to build the
建造者在这里，我们将建立
patch right so create page builder and
修补程序正确，因此创建页面构建器并
the first thing we are going to do we
我们要做的第一件事
are going to remove and we are going to
将要删除，我们将要
remove the last jason which is a little
删除最后一个杰森这是一点点
Argonauts we don't need him here
阿尔贡人我们在这里不需要他
and as a parameter we supply the pointer
作为参数我们提供了指针
to the object you want to remove and he
到您要删除的对象，他
is a number free in a released so it's
在发行版中是免费的，所以
like that right the second operation is
像这样，第二项操作是
going to be replaced and we are going to
将被替换，我们将
replace the profession of our first
取代我们的第一职业
Jason which is Jason Moore and replace
杰森（Jason）是杰森·摩尔（Jason Moore）并替换
it with maniac killer so he will become
它与疯狂的杀手，所以他将成为
a mini killer which is maybe right
一个迷你杀手，也许是正确的
because in the super agent he's keeping
因为他在超级经纪人中
a lot of people's of his sort of a
很多人都是他的
vernacular right and we are going we
白话权，我们要去
don't have we want we don't want to have
没有我们想要我们不想拥有
too many killers in our list so we will
我们列表中的杀手太多，所以我们会
replace a profession of Jason movies to
取代Jason电影的职业
super agent
超级特工
and it could be true as well because in
这也可能是正确的，因为
the movies it never said that he is not
电影里从来没有说过他不是
separation so maybe he is actually super
分离，所以也许他实际上是超级
agent doing some very complicated tasks
代理执行一些非常复杂的任务
or whether anyway so it looks like this
还是无论如何看起来像这样
okay it's so sad because I forgot I
好吧，很伤心，因为我忘了我
forgot to build right now it looks okay
忘了建现在看起来还好
and now we need to apply this patch to
现在我们需要将此补丁应用于
something right
对的东西
basically we similar pattern we are
基本上我们是相似的模式
using here all right patch apply and we
在这里使用所有适用的补丁程序，我们
applied it to out Jason's list right
将其应用到Jason的列表中
like that it will produce a new JSON
这样，它将产生一个新的JSON
array result right and we need to print
数组结果正确，我们需要打印
out with result to see that it's okay
结果出来就可以了
result to string right it looks okay so
结果正确串起来就好了
let's just run it and see how it works
让我们运行它，看看它如何工作
okay and this is number table number
好的，这是号码表号码
five okay so what we have here we have
五好，所以我们这里有
adjacent ball and here is a mania killer
相邻的球，这是躁狂症的杀手
works and we have Jason Voorhees and
作品，我们有Jason Voorhees和
he's a super agent great and we don't
他是一个超级超级经纪人，我们不
have Jason who is are going out so it
有杰森要出去，所以
seems working so this is how to use
似乎有效，所以这是使用方法
Jason patch and it looks like we
杰森补丁，看起来像我们
finished with Jason protesting demos and
完成了杰森抗议演示，
now we'll jump into Jason binding BMO
现在我们将跳入Jason绑定BMO
right and what is Jason binding Jason
对，Jason是什么约束Jason
binding key the framework which allows
绑定密钥允许的框架
you to buy the Jason to Java objects and
您购买Jason to Java对象并
vice versa so basically serialize and
反之亦然，所以基本上是序列化和
deserialize java objects to and from
将Java对象反序列化
Jason documents and this is the
杰森的文件，这是
sample where I actually have some pre
样本中我实际上有一些预
filled something's right and what is
填写正确的东西，什么是
that I just created the model classes
我刚刚创建了模型类
for our Jason's right so person class
为了我们的杰森的权利人类
which is which has a name and profession
哪个有名字和职业
and the list of phone numbers and phone
以及电话号码和电话列表
number is this it has type it has number
这是它的类型吗？
and what I did here I just pre field I
而我在这里所做的我只是预备我
created to Jason's list basically but
基本上是按照Jason的清单创建的
same as here right but Angela okay
和这里一样，但是安吉拉还可以
so assume that this Jason contains the
因此，假设这个Jason包含
same data as our Jason's JSON document
与我们Jason的JSON文档相同的数据
right and here I will demonstrate how to
对，在这里我将演示如何
serialize this into Jason and some
将其序列化为杰森和一些
customizations like formatting Jason
定制，例如格式化Jason
changing property names changing the now
更改属性名称更改现在
feels behavior this kind of stuff but
感觉这种东西的行为，但
we'll start with we need to actually
我们将首先需要
create with Jason binding agent Jason
用Jason粘合剂Jason创建
button instance first right and I'll in
按钮实例优先，然后我进入
Jason P over main processes Jason Jason
Jason P对主要流程的关注Jason Jason
vo main projects is Jason be right but
vo主要项目是Jason是正确的，但
it creates like a different way so Jason
它创造了一种不同的方式，所以杰森
B Jason B equals two it imports
B Jason B等于两个it进口
Jason B builder create it just creates
Jason B builder创建它只是创建
Jason B agent with default settings and
具有默认设置的Jason B代理和
we design Jason be the day that default
我们将杰森设计为违约之日
setting suitable for
设置适合
everything so which is the standard way
一切都这样，这是标准方式
of creating Jason and after that we need
杰森的创作，之后我们需要
to serialize out Jason's list and it can
序列化杰森的名单，它可以
be done like with Jason be to Jason and
就像与杰森一​​样对杰森和
we are passing our
我们正在通过我们的
Jason's list here and we say look just
杰森的清单在这里，我们说看起来
two lines of code and we need to print
两行代码，我们需要打印
it out like that and now let's see how
这样，现在让我们看看如何
it works if it works they just run it
如果可以，他们就运行它就可以了
okay and this is number 6 DM oh yeah it
好，这是6号DM哦，是的
produced JSON document which looks
产生的JSON文件看起来
absolutely the same as our Jason Jason
与我们的Jason Jason完全一样
but it's not formatted right so I can't
但它的格式不正确，所以我不能
really broken it let's just add some
真的坏了，我们只添加一些
customizations here and which produces
这里的定制以及产生的
we're formatted output right in order to
我们对输出进行了格式化，以便
do it we need to create Jason B
需要创建Jason B吗
configuration which is stored in Jason B
配置存储在Jason B中
config object so all configuration is
config对象，因此所有配置都是
there so we're creating in you Jason B
在那里，我们为您打造Jason B
configuration and so which is which is
配置，这是哪个
what you can configure look many things
您可以配置的东西看起来很多
clockwise order stick gene coding locale
顺时针方向棒基因编码区域
adapters blah blah blah many things here
适配器等等等等在这里
but we will use this one for now before
但我们将在此之前使用
marching through now we need to pass
前进，现在我们需要通过
this configuration to jason builder to
将此配置交给jason builder
create customized Jason B engine it can
创建可以定制的Jason B引擎
be done like this look it's very easy
看起来像这样很容易
and if we run it it's supposed to
如果我们运行它，应该
produce nicely formatted Jason let's
制作格式正确的Jason，让我们
take a look okay and this is number six
好的，这是第六
yeah so this is how our Jason looks like
是的，这就是我们的Jason的样子
looks it's nicely formatted now let's
看起来格式很好，现在让我们
see what if what if we want to change
看看如果我们想改变怎么办
the property name it eats phone numbers
吃电话的财产名称
but it's too long we would like that
但是我们想要那太久了
it is phones in the produced Jason
这是杰森生产的手机
documents how to do it of course I can
我当然可以记录如何做
change the property here right
在这里更改属性
but this is not nice much better day is
但这不是很好，更好的一天是
using Jason be property annotation which
使用杰森是属性注释
allows us to change the property name to
允许我们将属性名称更改为
funds right and if we're on our sample
资金正确，如果我们在样本中
now these phone numbers should be
现在这些电话号码应该是
replaced with false let's just take a
取而代之的是假的
look let's combine compare I hope that
看，让我们结合起来比较，我希望
if it compels immediately I have time to
如果它立即迫使我有时间
add another GMO to my demonstration but
在演示中添加另一个GMO，但
I can't do it okay so look it changed
我做不好，所以看起来变了
two phones right and then we think is
两部手机正确，然后我们认为是
that and you can put with notation not
那，你可以用符号不
only to feel itself you actually put it
只是觉得自己你真的把它
in together alright get phone numbers if
在一起可以得到电话号码
you put it here it will produce the same
你把它放在这里，它会产生相同的
result if you want to check it and then
结果，如果您想检查一下，然后
just run it again so this property can
只需再次运行它，以便此属性可以
be on Gator can be on the field itself
在Gator上可以在场上
can be on cetera if you put it on setter
如果放在塞特犬上就可以
we will expect that we will read from
我们希望我们会读
our property all these which is supplied
我们提供的所有这些财产
in the annotation so you can actually
在注释中，因此您实际上可以
read to from one property and write to
从一个属性读取并写入
another one I don't know do we need with
我不知道的另一个
your skin but it's allowed
你的皮肤，但允许
so she founds here at so you can click
所以她在这里找到了，所以你可以点击
to the ghetto another thing I want to
贫民窟，我想做的另一件事
demonstrate here if you look at that
如果你看这里示范
document that Jason it does he doesn't
证明Jason确实没有
have any phone numbers so funds property
有任何电话号码，因此可以财产
is not there at all because it's now by
根本不在那里，因为现在
default Jason be just skipping now
默认Jason现在就跳过
properties but what if you actually want
属性，但如果您确实想要
to have it there right so you read it
把它放在正确的位置，以便您阅读
from other application that expects it
从其他期望的应用程序
to be now right it was easy to change we
现在，改变我们很容易
just put Jason B
刚把杰森B
new label annotation on the class so all
类上的新标签注释，因此所有
properties which are now in the class
现在在类中的属性
now supposed to be a supposed to appear
现在应该是应该出现
in result injection document then just
在结果注入文件中
take a look I keep forgetting to creat
看看我一直忘了创造
yeah oops
是的，哎呀
you see that it has phones which is now
您会看到它现在有手机
now right so there are some more
现在，所以还有更多
annotations right for customization
定制的注释权
Jason the creator and blah blah blah
杰森（Jason）的创作者和等等等等
it's out of scope of adjustable of my
这超出了我的可调范围
demonstration now maybe I'll do another
现在演示，也许我会再做一次
demonstration to demonstrate you know
示范以证明你知道
other customizations but not today so I
其他自定义项，但不是今天，所以我
assume that we finish with serialization
假设我们完成序列化
and let's jump to another demo and Jason
让我们跳到另一个演示和Jason
we dis utilization them okay so this is
我们可以利用它们，所以这是
the nice thing what we are going to do
好事情，我们要做什么
here we are going to use Jason processor
在这里，我们将使用Jason处理器
and Jason reader together and by the way
和Jason Reader在一起，顺便说一句
I think I didn't mention that but Jason
我想我没有提到，但杰森
binding is using Jason Otteson in behind
绑定在后面使用Jason Otteson
so one anyway that's up to you what I'm
所以无论如何，取决于我
going to do I'm going to lead our
我要去带领我们
Jason's document using jason processor
使用Jason处理器的Jason文档
I'm going to use Jason pointer to get
我将使用Jason指针来获取
the first Jason or let's use the second
第一个杰森，或者我们使用第二个
case unless you don't get second Jason
除非你没有第二个杰森
using jason pointer and after that I'm
使用杰森指针，然后我
going to deserialize it by this to our
通过这个反序列化到我们
person object here right
这里的人对象
okay so again I will just copy paste
好吧，我再次复制粘贴
these beat right
这些打对了
which is getting which is creating a
越来越得到创造
reader and reading everything to Jason
读者并阅读所有内容给杰森
Rae and now we need to create a quiz
雷，现在我们需要创建一个测验
hell it in the demo here create an
它在演示中创建一个
adjacent pointer copy paste it here but
相邻指针复制将其粘贴到此处
instead of profession I will get whole
而不是专业，我会变得完整
other object so this is a pointer to the
其他对象，所以这是指向
second Jason Jason Wu he's right okay so
第二个Jason Jason Wu他没事，所以
now we need to change this because it's
现在我们需要更改它，因为
not profession let's call it mu he's
不是职业，我们称呼他为
right so which is Jason value of that
是的，那是杰森的价值
axis I think we can I guess that's okay
轴，我想我们可以猜到没关系
it's okay okay so we've got our who he
没关系没关系，所以我们知道了他
is now now we have to bind it to our
现在现在我们必须将其绑定到我们的
person object so we need to create a
人对象，所以我们需要创建一个
Jason B Jason B which is Jason B builder
Jason B Jason B是Jason B建设者
create right and now we need to do
创造权利，现在我们需要做
person person equals Jason B from Jason
人等于Jason中的Jason B
in this case right and we need to get
在这种情况下，我们需要
out Jason here which is which is to
杰森在这里，这是要
string and we need to actually for D
字符串，我们实际上需要为D
serialization we need to pass a type a
序列化我们需要传递一个类型
target type here with this person dot
此人的目标类型在此点
class right so this is our Jason movies
上课权利，所以这是我们的杰森电影
to check that it works let's just print
检查它是否起作用，让我们打印
it out person I'm sure that it has to
我敢肯定，必须
street method okay doesn't have it so we
街头法好吧没有，所以我们
can just quickly add it like this
可以像这样快速添加它
it's like this and let's run it
就像这样，让我们​​运行它
creatures and run it
生物并运行它
okay so this is number six okay
好的，这是第六个
wrong demo so sexy number seven here
错误的演示，所以性感的数字在这里七
okay and you see that it's actually you
好吧，你看到它实际上是你
find it's actually works so we do she
发现它确实有效，所以我们做到了
realized so it doesn't print anything
意识到，所以它不打印任何东西
here but which is supposed to be my
在这里，但这应该是我的
design so phone numbers are there so
设计所以电话号码在那里
what we've done just now again we just
我们刚才所做的只是
use JSON parser to read JSON document we
使用JSON解析器读取JSON文档
you Jason pointer to extract some bit of
你杰森指针提取一些
that and we use JSON by binding to buy
然后我们通过绑定使用JSON来购买
this data to our Java objects here okay
将此数据发送到我们的Java对象中
and now it looks like we have our last
现在看来，我们已经有了最后一个
demo which is the D serialization with
演示是D序列化
generics again we are going to what we
泛型再次我们要去我们
are going to use here we are going to
将在这里使用，我们将
use our favorite Jason's document and
使用我们最喜欢的Jason的文档并
this time we are going to dis realize it
这次我们要意识到
into the list of person so it's a
进入人员列表，所以这是一个
generic list right okay let's do it
通用列表好吧，让我们做吧
first of all we need to create a jason
首先，我们需要创建一个杰森
be edging jason be using jason be
使用jason be磨边jason
builder recently builder create right
建设者最近建设者创建权
here our comes okay let's just do to say
来了，我们可以说
we need to dis realized our jason's
我们需要意识到我们的杰森
jason jason file to a list of person
jason jason文件到一个人的名单
list of person Jason's
杰森的人的名单
supposed to be Jason B from Jason and we
应该是Jason的Jason B，我们
need to pass our stream here so let's
需要在这里传递信息流，所以让我们
just do it as I usually do
照常做
Jason's Jason right and we need to pass
杰森（Jason）的杰森（Jason）对，我们需要通过
a type of whether it is realizing to
一种是否正在意识到
hear it was very easy for the normal
听到这对于正常人来说非常容易
type like this but for generic type is a
像这样的类型，但对于通用类型是
little bit different because a generic
有点不同，因为通用
type and you know this genetic
类型，你知道这个遗传
information usually is lost when we are
当我们在时，信息通常会丢失
passing it to like like this way right
像这样以正确的方式传递它
so in order to do it properly what we
所以为了正确地做我们
have to do we have to do it this way we
必须要做的，我们必须这样做
have to doesn't know what the type is
不必知道类型是什么
okay side we it actually create array
好吧，我们实际上创建了数组
list of person
人员清单
so basically instance in a sink right
所以基本上是一个沉没的实例
and after that get it's a generic
然后得到一个通用的
superclass like this like this and we
这样的超类，我们
need to pass it here and in this case it
需要通过这里，在这种情况下
will properly work right to check it
将正确检查它
let's just print out let's go to say the
让我们打印出来让我们说
first name the name of the first Jason
名字第一个Jason的名字
get the first element and
得到第一个元素
it's cause to be Jason's and get name
成为杰森的名字
right let's just run it to see that it
正确，让我们运行它以查看它
works here competition is okay so it's
在这里工作竞争还可以，所以
number 8 VMO Jason board so it works to
8号VMO Jason板，因此可以
check it then just print out the name of
检查一下，然后打印出名称
a second second Jason it's a poster
第二秒钟杰森是海报
print out Jason Voorhees here
在此处打印Jason Voorhees
okay so number eight Jason movies okay
好，所以八部杰森电影好了
I'm sorry so it looks like we've done
对不起，看来我们已经完成了
everything what's planned so as I said
正如我所说的，所有计划
II I will upload this demonstration to
II我将把这个演示上传到
this source code repository so you can
此源代码存储库，因此您可以
reference it any time and thanks for
随时参考，谢谢
watching it if you have any questions or
观看它，如果您有任何疑问或
if you have any suggestions you always
如果您有任何建议，您总是
can go to our website which is Jason B
可以去我们的网站Jason B
dot that and it contains everything
点它并包含所有内容
about this binding it has references to
关于此绑定，它具有对
arrived implementations I'm getting
我得到的实现
started guides and so on anyway so
反正开始了指南等等
thanks for watching and see you later
感谢您的收看，稍后见
bye bye
再见